Grey hair can be the beginning of the end. A silver signal that youth and beauty are fading and only old age remains.
白发可能是衰老的开端，这一银色信号预示着青春与美丽正在消逝，唯有岁月留存。
And while grey at 60 may not be surprising, many start to turn prematurely as young as 20.
60岁长出白发或许不足为奇，但很多人早在20岁就出现了早生华发的情况。
If we want to hide it, modern haircare products allow us to easily cover up our natural grey and preserve our youth a little longer.
如果想掩盖白发，现代护发产品能让我们轻松遮盖自然发色，将青春多保留一段时间。
But these days, many people – and women in particular, are ditching the dye to show their natural colours.
但如今，许多人——尤其是女性，开始放弃染发，展现自然发色。
Why?
这是为什么呢？
"Research has shown that our hair follicle production can be influenced by factors such as hormones and stress, but some people have a genetic predisposition to lose pigment or go bald more than others," says a report on the BBC website.
英国广播公司网站的一份报告称：“研究表明，毛囊的色素生成会受到激素和压力等因素影响，但有些人天生就更容易色素流失或秃顶。”
In addition, Prof Desmond Tobin, a hair and skin pigmentation specialist at the University of Bradford in the UK, says that it is normal for people with a European background to start greying in their early 20s.
此外，英国布拉德福德大学的头发与皮肤色素专家德斯蒙德·托宾教授表示，欧洲血统的人在20岁出头开始长白发是正常现象。
Research which he participated in found that different races have different average ageing rates - with African and East-Asian backgrounds tending to whiten later.
他参与的研究发现，不同种族的平均衰老速度存在差异——非洲和东亚血统的人头发变白的时间往往更晚。
For many men, going grey may not be a big deal.
对许多男性来说，长白发可能并不是什么大不了的事。
It's now seen as a sign of sophistication, says UK newspaper Metro. It uses adjectives such as rugged, unique and fashionable.
英国《都市报》称，如今白发被视为成熟老练的象征，并用“粗犷、独特、时尚”等词汇来形容。
But for many women, these qualities don't seem to apply.
但对许多女性而言，这些特质似乎并不适用。
Kate Dinota, a New Yorker who started turning grey when she was seven, states that the everyday woman feels a pressure not to age.
纽约人凯特·迪诺塔7岁就开始长白发，她说普通女性普遍面临着“不能显老”的压力。
At 28 and after 14 years, she decided to stop dying her hair and let her grey hair show.
28岁时，在坚持染发14年后，她决定不再染发，坦然露出白发。
And she's not alone.
而这样做的并非只有她一人。
Since 2008, worldwide search interest in 'grey hair' has increased dramatically, Google Trends shows.
谷歌趋势数据显示，自2008年以来，全球对“白发”的搜索热度大幅上升。
This may have been driven by celebrities such as Ariana Grande and Lady Gaga, who have both had silver locks.
这可能是受到了爱莉安娜·格兰德和Lady Gaga等名人的推动，她们都曾留过银发造型。
"People are torturing their hair to get the look," says renowned hair colourist Rita Hazan, who has worked with celebrities such as Beyoncé and Mariah Carey.
“人们为了打造这种造型，把头发折腾得够呛，”著名染发师丽塔·哈赞说，她曾为碧昂斯、玛丽亚·凯莉等名人服务。
Indeed, this trend was what persuaded 30-year-old Stephanie Tunchez from Texas to stop dying her natural hair two-and-a-half years ago.
事实上，正是这一趋势促使30岁的得克萨斯州人斯蒂芬妮·通切斯在两年半前停止了染发，回归自然发色。
But to many women, the transition is not an easy one.
但对许多女性来说，从染发过渡到自然白发并非易事。
Indeed, Kate experienced doubt from others with her initial decision.
事实上，凯特最初做出这个决定时，就遭到了他人的质疑。
"People were like, 'Are you sure?
“人们会说‘你确定吗？
What about your career?
你的事业怎么办？
You're so young!' Like that seems silly," she reports.
你还这么年轻！’这话听着真可笑，”她回忆道。
She believes there needs to be better representation of grey-haired women of all ages.
她认为，各个年龄段的白发女性都需要更多的正面形象展示。
In this way it is hoped that, like many men, women will feel more confident about letting it show and will feel more comfortable going grey gracefully.
希望通过这种方式，女性也能像许多男性一样，更有信心展现自然白发，更从容地优雅老去。